[
  {
    "question": "A ⊆ B means ",
    "category": "Maths",
    "options": [
      "A is superset of B ",
      "A is subset of B",
      " A and B are disjoint sets ",
      "A is improper subset of B"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "A is subset of B"
  },
  {
    "question": "Two matrix A and B are equal if ",
    "category": "Maths",
    "options": [
      "They are square matrix ",
      "They have same order",
      "  Their corresponding elements are equal",
      "They have same number of columns"
    ],
    "correct_answer": "Their corresponding elements are equal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Degree of x4 + 2x - 1 is",
    "category": "Maths",
    "options": ["0", "-1", "2", "4"],
    "correct_answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "The quadratic eq. Having roots 2 and - is",
    "category": "Maths",
    "options": [
      "-x2 + x - 6 = 0",
      " X2 + x - 6 = 0",
      "X2 - x - 6 = 0 ",
      " X2 + x + 6 = 0 "
    ],
    "correct_answer": " X2 + x - 6 = 0 "
  },
  {
    "question": "The general term of a sequence is denoted by",
    "category": "Maths",
    "options": ["an", "na", "Sn", "a+d"],
    "correct_answer": "an"
  },
  {
    "question": " A coin is tossed five times, total no. of outcomes is",
    "category": "Maths",
    "options": ["4", "32", "8", "16"],
    "correct_answer": "32"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many kind of trignometry are there?",
    "category": "Maths",
    "options": ["Only One", "Four", "Two", "Three"],
    "correct_answer": "Two"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cos (- β) =",
    "category": "Maths",
    "options": ["-cos β", "cos β", "Sin β", "-Sin β"],
    "correct_answer": "cos β"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 sin 30cos30 =",
    "category": "Maths",
    "options": ["sin60", "cos60", "-sin60", "cot30"],
    "correct_answer": "sin60"
  },
  {
    "question": "Range of cot θ is",
    "category": "Maths",
    "options": ["R", "Q", "N", "Z"],
    "correct_answer": "N"
  },
  {
    "question": "A subset of A x B is called a",
    "category": "Maths",
    "options": ["Binary Relation", "Range", "Domain", "Digit"],
    "correct_answer": "Binary Relation"
  },
  {
    "question": "x-coordinate of a point is also called",
    "category": "Maths",
    "options": ["Ordinate", "Origin", "Component", "Abscissa"],
    "correct_answer": "Abscissa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fifth order derivative of x4 is",
    "category": "Maths",
    "options": ["0", "24", "24x", "12x"],
    "correct_answer": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "If f(x) is decreasing in (a, b) then i",
    "category": "Maths",
    "options": ["F`(c) = 0 ", " F`(c) > 0 ", "F`(c)=1 ", "F`(c)<0"],
    "correct_answer": "F`(c)<0"
  },
  {
    "question": "A plane cutting the cone parallel to its axis gives a",
    "category": "Maths",
    "options": ["Ellipse", "Parabola", "Circle", "Hyperbola"],
    "correct_answer": "Hyperbola"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which word has SAME meaning as CANNY",
    "category": "English",
    "options": ["Stout", "Clever", "Handsome", "Obstinate"],
    "correct_answer": "Handsome"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the synonym of LUDICROUS ",
    "category": "English",
    "options": ["Dismal", "Clear", "Absurd", "Clear"],
    "correct_answer": "Absurd"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the synonym of COMELY",
    "category": "English",
    "options": ["Delightful", "Homely", "Elegant", "Pretty"],
    "correct_answer": "Pretty"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the synonym of Affluent",
    "category": "English",
    "options": ["Cupid", "Poor", "Bawdy", "Prosperous"],
    "correct_answer": "Prosperous"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the synonym of chaotic",
    "category": "English",
    "options": ["Arranged", "Settled", "Disordered", "Organized"],
    "correct_answer": "Disordered"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the synonym of shrunk",
    "category": "English",
    "options": ["Maximize", "Wide", "Exploit", "Dwindled"],
    "correct_answer": "Dwindled"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the synonym of Applauded?",
    "category": "English",
    "options": ["Clapped", "Slapped", "Smiled", "Kicked"],
    "correct_answer": "Clapped"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the OPPOSITE of Peaked",
    "category": "English",
    "options": ["Tired", "Pointy", "Arrogant", "Ruddy"],
    "correct_answer": "Ruddy"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the OPPOSITE of Flaunt",
    "category": "English",
    "options": ["Whip", "Flatten", "Hiden", "Showoff"],
    "correct_answer": "Hide"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the OPPOSITE of Gumption",
    "category": "English",
    "options": ["Seriousness", "Apathy", "Despair", "Peaked"],
    "correct_answer": "Peaked"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the OPPOSITE of Quisling",
    "category": "English",
    "options": ["Loyalist", "Adherent", "Faithful", "Follower"],
    "correct_answer": "Loyalist"
  },
  {
    "question": "x-coordinate of a point is also called",
    "category": "English",
    "options": ["Ordinate", "Origin", "Component", "Abscissa"],
    "correct_answer": "Abscissa"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the OPPOSITE of Finagle",
    "category": "English",
    "options": ["Fudge", "Refrain", "Wangle", "Chicane"],
    "correct_answer": "Refrain"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the OPPOSITE of Rogue",
    "category": "English",
    "options": ["Saint", "Wastrel", "Louse", "Reprobate"],
    "correct_answer": "Saint"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the OPPOSITE of Demented",
    "category": "English",
    "options": ["Sensible", "Authentic", "Attract", "Extract"],
    "correct_answer": "Sensible"
  }
]
